experimentalbiology.org 2011-12-16

# 

This Privacy Statement relates solely to the online information collection and use practices of our Web site located at www.eb2009.org (this "Web Site"), and not to any subdomains of this Web Site. We recognize that many visitors and users of this Web Site are concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Statement, which may be updated from time to time, has been developed to address those concerns.

Your use of this Web Site indicates to us that you have read and accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Statement. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact: [jkearney@faseb.org](mailto:jkearney@faseb.org). **  
**

## WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU DO WE COLLECT?

When you visit our Web Site, you may provide us with two types of information: (1) personally identifiable information that you knowingly choose to disclose, which is collected on an individual basis for our exhibition, and (2) general user information that does not contain personally identifiable information, which is collected on an aggregate basis as you browse the Web Site.

|  | 

## Personally Identifiable Information You Choose to Provide.

We may ask for certain personal information from you for the purpose of providing to you content and/or services that you request. For example, if you indicate an interest in receiving press releases about The Association of Biomolecular Resource Facilities, you are asked to submit your name and e-mail address, which we retain on file, so that we may send you the information that you requested. Information submitted to reserve booths are stored on file in our database. We may retain a record of users who have contacted us in order to respond properly to questions or concerns and for purposes of future communications. Your information is not released or shared with third parties for any purposes.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information We Collect.

Web server logs: Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web Site utilizes standard technology called Web server logs to collect information about how our Web Site is used. Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web Site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web Site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

You can, of course, disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of our Web Site will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. You should consult with your browser's provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies.  
  
---|---  
  
## HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

We use your personally identifiable information to provide you with the information or services that you have requested, and, in some cases, to contact you about our annual programs or services.

We use non-identifying information collected on our Web Site in the aggregate to better understand your use of the Web Site and to enhance your enjoyment and experience. For example, we may use the information to improve the design and content of our Web Site or to analyze the programs and services that we offer.

We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Our employees, agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect the information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement.

We may provide access to your personally identifiable information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web Site, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights, or to protect the rights and safety of visitors to this Web Site or the public. In those instances, the information is provided only for that limited purpose.

We will not share your personally identifiable information in ways unrelated to those described above without providing you with an opportunity to opt out of such use or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## DATA SECURITY

We take reasonable steps to maintain the security of the personally identifiable information that we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as installing electronic security systems that guard against unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, so you do so at your own risk.

## CONSENT TO TRANSFER

This Web Site is operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Web Site, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

## LINKS

This Web Site contains links to third party sites as well as to other sites owned and/or operated by The Association of Biomolecular Resource Facilities. Please be aware that The Association of Biomolecular Resource Facilities is not responsible for the privacy practices of any third party sites. Please also be aware that the privacy policies of other EB sites may differ significantly from the privacy policy of this Web Site. Therefore, we encourage our users to read the privacy statement of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by this Web Site.
